Guide to the Council for Ecumenical Student Christian Ministry Records - Addendum A
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Addendum: Clyde Robinson Files, 1985-1991; Series VII
  - CESCM staff report; minutes of steering committee; options for NCCC-ES; letters re. meetings; NCCC-ES minutes of executive committee, 1987 Jun (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - WSCF letter re. global ecumenical youth meeting; campus visits schedule CESCM; letters of steering committee members; proposal for uniting NCCC-ES and UME and report on meeting, 1987 Jul (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - NCCC-ES program committee agenda; letters planning for National Ecumenical Campus Ministry Conference; CESCM staff report, 1987 Aug (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Incl. re. future of WSCF NA, NCCC-ES, report of steering committee of a "New Thing", 1987 Sep (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Letters re. CESCM conference planning and campus visits; report re. direction of WSCF NA; minutes of CESCM planning committee meeting, 1987 Oct (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Report of steering committee of a "New Thing"; summary of CESCM minutes; CESCM staff report to UME; feedback on "New Thing", 1987 Nov (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Minutes of CESCM planning committee; steering committee; "New Thing" notes; letters, 1987 Dec (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Incl. re. CESCM budget, organizational plan for "New Thing"; press release of "For a Call to Dialogue and Renewed Partnerships", 1988 Jan (Box 29, Folder 18-19)
  - Incl. re. advisory consultation UME, NCCC-ES, CESCM, 1988 Feb (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Consensus on organizational plan; transition timetable; letters re. consultation, financial report CESCM, 1988 Mar (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - WSCF working paper on re. history and new phase:"The Current Ecumenical Scene"; consultation planning; letters re. WSCF, 1988 Apr (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - CESCM steering committee meeting; letters re. consultation; schedule for consultation, 1988 May (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Proposal for National Ecumenical Campus Ministry Conference; steering committee minutes; consultation report, 1988 Jun (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Planning for National Ecumenical Student conference; proposals for CESCM sponsored National Ecumenical Leadership Development program, 1988 Jul-Sep (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Incl. CESCM statement of purpose, 1988 Oct-Dec (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Proposals for 1989 CESCM sponsored National Ecumenical Leadership Development Program for students; Peacemaking in Education Program; CESCM Partners meeting minutes, 1989 Feb-Apr (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Incl. CESCM steering committee minutes; reports on "The Big Event" (WSCF European student conference); staff report; CESCM financial report, 1989 May-Dec (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Incl. CESCM proposed budget, financial report; WSCF Centennial Fund, letters, 1990-1991 (Box 30, Folder 29)
- Addendum 2011, 1986-2009; Series VIII
  - CESCM background documents, by-laws, statement of purpose, 1986-2007 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence of Douglas Fenton including with Student Christian Movement of Canada, re. Young Adult Ecumenical Forum, and re. relationship with WSCF, 2005-2008 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence of Dennis Landon including regarding relationship of CESCM with WSCF, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - CESCM meetings in New York (spring) and Chicago (fall), 2005 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - CESCM meetings in New Orleans (spring and fall), 2006 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - CESCM meetings in Nashville (spring) and St. Louis (fall - strategic planning workshop), 2007 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - CESCM meeting in New York, 2008 Apr (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Minutes of "Conversation between ECMT and remaining CESCM members", Chicago, 2009 Mar (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - CESCM financial statements, 2005-2009 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Related organizations: Council of Higher Education Ministries (CHEM): correspondence, organizational documents, financial statements, 1992-2008 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Related organizations: Higher Education Ministries Arena (HEMA): organizational documents, financial statements, 2005-2008 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Related organizations: National Campus Ministry Association: Minutes of NCMA Coordinating Committee, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Related organizations: National Council of Churches, USA: Educational Leadership Ministries Commission and Ecumenical Campus Ministries Team: financial information, 2006-2008 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Related organizations: Student Christian Movement of Canada: periodicals, 1989-2007 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Related organizations: World Student Christian Federation / WSCF North American Regional Committee / WSCF North America Regional Office, 2006-2008 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Related organizations: Student Christian Movement of India, Student Christian Movement (British), 1989-1993, no date (Box 31, Folder 16)